打烊啦
That's it for tonight.
是时候来数数小费了
Time to count the tip jar.
手部避孕套
Hand condom.
你真是让人咋舌啊
I can't believe you.
直到现在还采取安全措施
Using protection is so five years ago.
这里是威廉斯堡
This is Williamsburg.
连钱都可能携带性病病毒的
There's a good chance even the dollars have herpes.
如果那些单身钱都有性病
Well, if those singles have herpes,
那他们应该把病情隐瞒到结婚之日
They should just lie about it till they get married
就像所有人一样
Like everybody else does.
噢 太好了 你们还没打烊
Oh, good, you're still open.
噢 是的 还没 您需要什么?
Oh, yes, we are. What can I get you?
收银机里的全部钱
Everything in the register.
噢 我去 潮人都来打劫了
Oh, my god. It's a hipster hold-up.
把钱交出来 我有钱枪
Hand it over. I have a gun.
我就想死 所以你这招不管用
Well, I have a death wish so that's not gonna work.
朋友 我们在这蛋糕窗口
Look, pal, we work at this cupcake window
从两点工作到四点 每周工作六晚
from 2:00 to 4:00, six nights a week,
而且还是在旁边家破餐厅辛苦工作
and that is after eight hours of slinging hash
八小时后 就赚那么点点的钱
at the diner next door for lousy minimum wage,
可是那群有钱的政客 身处... 帮帮我
which a bunch of rich politicians out in... Help me out.
华盛顿
Washington.
就她说的那地方... 不给我们涨薪
What she said... don't wanna raise.
然后我们还得走回自己的非法单间
Then, we walk home to our illegal one bedroom apartment,
靠着吃感冒药才能睡上三小时
get three hours of nyquil induced sleep
之后起床 我们只能分食一碗
before we have to get back up and share a bowl
西班牙语版的脆谷乐
of spanish language cheerios.
都是脆谷乐 只是包装盒印有墨西哥帽
It's the same thing but the "C" Wears a sombrero.
所以 我不会把这血汗钱给你
So, no, I am not about to give you our hard-earned money.
如果你要开枪打我 最好瞄准点
And if you're gonna shoot me, better aim good.
否则 如果你失手了 我就会翻出这个柜台
'cause if you miss, I will climb over this counter,
揪下你的脑袋 用来做新的小费瓫
tear off your head, and it'll be our new tip jar.
好吧 我刚打劫了披萨店
Yeah, I just robbed pizza pizza.
这是二十块钱
Here's a $20.
祝你晚上愉快
Have a good night.
我对付人很有一套
I have a way with people.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
时间轴: Pisces夜
翻译: xingzhenhang 酱油影
校对: 桃茜茜
我刚看到咱们纸杯蛋糕的竞争对手
Look, I just saw that our cupcake competition,
那家布鲁克林的美味结业了
"Brooklyn Bitty Bites," went out of business.
是啊 那变成了一家卖药用大麻的
Yup, it's being changed into a medical marijuana store.
我这还有一张集孔卡
I already have my hole-punch card.
布朗尼蛋糕买四赠一
Buy four brownies and the fifth buzz is free.
布鲁克林的美味倒闭啦!
Brooklyn Bitty Bites beat it!
耶! 我们赢了!
Yeah! We won!
见鬼去吧 红毛女还有你的亚洲闺女!
Eat it, red haired lady and your asian daughter!
Max 这店是紧跟着纸杯蛋糕巨头
Max, them going down right after the death
克兰布斯店倒闭关门的 太吓人了
of the cupcake giant, "Crumbs," is scary.
就像是一个连环杀手在追杀
It's like there's a serial killer out there
纸杯蛋糕
coming after cupcakes.
那他应该很容易逃脱
Well, he should be easy to outrun,
因为有个胖胖的嗜血法医
'cause that'll be one fat dexter.
严肃点 我们要摊上大麻烦了
Seriously, we have a big problem.
我回来啦!
I'm back!
我们的小麻烦来了
And there's our little problem.
一般很难看到腹语表演者的玩偶
Wow, you don't usually see the ventriloquist's dummy
独自从箱子里跑出来的
out of his suitcase alone.
哈喽 Earl 哈喽 Caroline
Hello, Earl. Hello, Caroline.
你好 你这个劝我在上班前要接受三小时
Hello, reason I do two hours of phone therapy
电话治疗的人
every Wednesday before work.
大家想我吗
So, did you all miss me?
你有出门吗?
You were gone?
我发誓我昨天还见到你
'cause I swear I just saw you yesterday.
等等 有可能我见到的是猫
Wait, maybe that was a cat.
我出门了 同志们!
I was gone, people!
去旧金山参加一个会议
To San Francisco for a convention.
餐饮协会
The restaurant and diner association.
简称为"拉丝"
"RADASS."
你在旧金山参加了一个叫"拉丝"的东东?
You were at something called "RADASS" In san francisco?
你确定它不是叫拉稀？
Are you sure it wasn't "Redass"?
我不是去搞基 我只是关心餐厅发展
I am not gay. I'm restaurant curious.
我找到了一个适合咱们餐厅的新菜
I discovered an exciting new item for our menu.
不要 菜单已经满了
No way. No new menu additions.
我都担心得睡不着觉了
I already lie awake in bed
担心食物堆积得过高
worrying about how high the food bar is here.
端菜! 手撕猪肉
Pick up! Pulled pork.
这道菜味道会很好 因为我在撕之前
And it's good 'cause before I pulled it,
因为我已经给它做了个干擦
I gave it a dry rub.
新菜是标价四美元的土司
It's $4 toast.
四美元的土司?
$4 toast?
比我们现在的土司还贵五美元
That's $5 more than our toast is worth.
美味的手工面包
Delicious, homemade artisan bread.
起初 我有点人抗拒把这么大的玩意塞进嘴里
At first, I was reluctant to put something so big in my mouth.
但是当那热呼呼的奶油顺着我的下巴流下
But the hot butter drizzling down my chin
是我黏糊的嘉奖
was my sticky reward.
Han 这个土司太前卫了
Han, that toast is trendy foodie food.
它会死在这里的 正如我的灵魂
It'll die here, like my soul did.
我们的顾客都是些庸人 凡人
Our customers are just plain, normal people.
嘿 同志们!
Hey, everybody!
以及苏菲
And Sophie.
你猜怎么着?
Guess what?
有78个人在交友应用上给我点喜欢
78 guys want me on Tinder.
噢 79!
Oh, 79!
现在是80!
Now it's 80!
你用交友应用多久了?
How long have you been on Tinder?
10分钟!
Ten minutes!
噢 看啊 噢 我的天啊!
Oh, look, oh, my gosh!
这家伙是个水管工 是真的吗
This guy's a plumber. Are you kidding me?
好的 牵线成功!
Yes, that's a match!
这男人连衣服都没穿
And this guy isn't even wearing a shirt!
又一个成功!
That's another big yes!
天啊 姑娘们 我要去自己的专座
Oh, gosh, girls, I'll be over here,
坐着欣赏这些小鲜肉们
Looking at boys in my booth.
嘿 我知道有个女的在交友应用上遇到她老公
Hey, I know a girl who met her husband on Tinder.
不对 她是在那看见她老公
No, wait, she saw her husband on Tinder.
嘿 轮椅是不是也很性感?
Hey, are wheelchairs sexy?
我觉得这得看是谁坐在那上面
I guess it depends on who's in one.
我拒绝了
I say no.
先不点了
Hold the presses.
我刚收到我闺蜜发的新推特
I just got a new tweet from my gal,
她叫金·卡戴珊
Kim Kardashian.
噢 她刚从曼哈顿买了好多靴子
Oh, she just bought her some new boots in Manhattan.
金·卡戴珊是个传奇
Kim Kardashian is epic.
她上了"服饰与美容"的封面 火到不行
She was on the cover of Vogue. She's on fire.
那又怎样? 我也曾经火过
So? I've been on fire.
那是我最后一次试图用魔法获得免费零食
That's the last time I try witchcraft for the free snacks.
我爱卡戴珊家族
I love the Kardashians.
她们就像肯尼迪家族一样 只不过屁股更大
They're like the Kennedys but with bigger asses.
下次给我发信息
Text me next time.
打电话会让我抓狂
This whole talking thing is insane.
嗨
Hi!
请问一下我要怎么才能联系
Who would I talk to about finding the owner
Max手工蛋糕店的老板
of Max's homemade cupcakes?
这位就是Max 我是Caroline
That's Max. I'm Caroline.
我们是这家店的老板
We're the owners of this store.
穷得只剩四双袜子
And about four pairs of socks.
好极了 非常好 这家店很可爱
Great. Wonderful. Such a cute shop.
你们是否有兴趣让一个很受欢迎的...
Would you be interested in having a popular...
好的
Yes.
我还没说完
I didn't finish my sentence.
抱歉 我只是很久没听到"受欢迎"这几个字眼了
Sorry, I just haven't heard the word "popular" in so long.
嗯 是啊 她太老土了
Oh, yeah, she's over.
她是那种会去租录像带的人
She's the Blockbuster video of people.
请问你们是否有兴趣让一个
Would you be interested in having
很受欢迎的真人秀在本店拍摄?
a popular reality show filmed here?
好...
Y...
非常抱歉 我得接个电话
I'm so sorry. I have to take this.
一分钟
Just a minute.
搞毛啊
What?
说吧 快点
Just say it already. Come on.
Max 这太好啦 想想曝光度
Max, this is great. Think of the exposure.
我比较好奇是哪部真人秀
I wonder which reality show it is.
也许"少女妈妈"正在拍摄
Ooh, maybe 16 and Pregnant is doing
"看看她们的近况"环节 然后找上了我
a "Where are they now" segment and they found me.
或者是找你的 "平胸甜心来了"
Or that one about you, "Here comes honey boobless."
你到底知道我是谁吗?
Do you have any idea who I am?
照我说的做 不然滚出去
You just do what I say or you are out!
好
Okay.
妈妈爱你
Mommy loves you.
抱歉 我孩子是尼日利亚人
Sorry, my baby's Nigerian.
要想住在这里 就得学英语
I mean, if you're gonna live here, learn the language.
天啊
Jeez.
你们意下如何?
So what are we thinking?
大爱 我们加入 哪个节目?
We'd love it. We're in. What show?
与卡戴珊姐妹同行
Keeping Up with the Kardashians.
上帝终于为我们开了一扇门
Finally, God opens a door.
所以我要关一扇窗
And I'm closing a window.
Max 住手!
Max!
她是个忠粉 所以太激动了
She's overwhelmed. Big fan.
有名片吗?
Do you have a card?
给 听着 给我发短信
Mm-hmm. And listen, text me.
别打电话 我会抓狂的
Don't call. It freaks me out.
给我一个理由
Just give me one good reason
为什么不和卡戴珊姐妹同行
why we shouldn't keep up with the Kardashians.
我可以给你五个
I'll give you five good reasons.
金 坎伯 克朗代克...
Kim, Kamber, Klondike...
小的那俩叫"香脆"和"奶油"
and the little ones, Krispy and Kreme.
根本不对
Not even close.
好吧 金 饼干 "酷爱"饮料
Fine. Kim, Kooky, Kool aid,
小的那俩叫"船长"和"袋鼠"
and the little ones, Kaptain and Kangaroo.
是金 克特妮 克洛伊 克莱和克恩黛儿
It's Kim, Kourtney, Khloe, Kylie, and Kendall.
她们的妈妈真大胆 竟然给一个也许
That mother has some nerve, naming a kid
从未看过Kindle电子书的孩子起这名字
who's probably never even read a book "Kindle."
我们需要这个机会
We need this.
所有人都看"与卡戴珊姐妹同行"
Everyone watches Keeping Up with the Kardashians.
就像没有明星版的
It's like Dancing with the Stars,
"与星共舞"
but without the stars.
与星星共舞
So, dancing with the stars.
好吧 这让我讨厌的节目 你给我说个优点出来
Okay, tell me one good thing about this show that I hate,
因为我从来没看过
'cause I've never seen it.
这个秀讲的是一个家庭
Well, it's all about this family
他们努力地想要...
and their struggle to...
同行
keep up.
好吧 我也没看过
Yeah, okay. I've never seen it either.
Sophie 真是太感谢你了 让我们在下班后
Sophie, thank you so much for letting us come up
到你家来看电视
after work to watch your TV.
Max把我们的旧电视给炸了
Max turned our old one into a bong.
那时候我也火了一把
That was another time I was on fire.
你们想看哪一集?
Well, which episode do you want to watch?
"金买了新帽子"
"Kim gets a new hat."
还是"克莱在科切拉音乐节痛哭"?
Or "Kylie cries at Coachella"?
还是"克洛伊来了次比基尼蜜蜡脱毛"?
Or "Khloe gets a bikini wax"?
这集太经典了
Now that one's a classic.
你录了多少集?
How many of these do you have DVR'd?
这个电视录了17集
Well, I got 17 on this TV
卧室里那个录了53集
and 53 on the one in the bedroom.
我喜欢听着金的声音入睡
I like to go to sleep with the sound of Kim's voice.
她说这句话的时候太怡人了
It's so comforting when she says,
"真是超级尴尬的"
"this is super awkward."
要知道她有时候会弯下腰
And you know, sometimes she arches her back
做这个动作说
when she says it, like this.
"真是超级尴尬的"
"This is super awkward."
真是超级尴尬的
This is super awkward.
我打赌如果我留在波兰
You know, I bet you if I stayed in Poland,
我和姐妹们也会有自己的真人秀
my sisters and I would have had our own show.
名字就是"与卡金斯基姐妹同行"
It would've been called, Keeping Up with the Kachinskis.
可惜她们没活到20岁就死了
It's too bad we all didn't live to see 20.
真不好
It's not cute.
你知道我想有人能逗笑我
You know I need someone to make me laugh.
金在哪儿? 她老是迟到
Where's Kim? Kim is always late.
住手!
Stop!
谢谢 各位
Thanks, guys.
就这样 结束了 给钱吧
That's it, we're done. Money.
嘿 你们出去! 都早上了!
Hey, get the hell out! It's morning!
我知道 但是看着她们无所事事
I know, I know, but we couldn't stop
让我们看上瘾了
watching them do nothing.
这真人秀太厉害了!
This show is freaking genius!
金发妹子是在哭吗?
Is the blonde one crying?
恩 克丽斯和金在维也纳的时候
Mm-hmm. Kris and Kim are in Vienna
有人偷了克丽斯的宝缇嘉定制包
and someone stole Kris's Bottega bag
香奈儿手包 以及她在巴黎买的
and her Chanel clutch with the matching pumps
配套高跟鞋
that she bought in Paris.
好吧 我要去吃早晨醒神药了
All right, well, I have to go take my morning tinkle.
但我回来的时候 你们必须得走
But when I come back, I want you two to be out of here
因为我需要那个秋千做运动
because I need that swing for my exercises.
我们必须参与这个真人秀
We have to do this show.
对我们的生意很有好处
It'll be so great for our business.
否则要想得到同样的曝光度
The only way we'd get more exposure
除非是奥兰多·布鲁姆和贾斯汀·比伯
is if Orlando Bloom and Bieber bitchslapped each other
在我们店门口对扇耳光
in front of our shop.
谁还管我们的生意呀?
Who cares about our business?
我要那妈收养我!
I want that mother to adopt me!
她家小孩拍了个性爱录像带 她能用它赚了几百万
Her kid makes a sex tape, she turns it into millions.
我拍了个性爱录像带 我妈竟然只是
The only thing my mother ever did with my sex tape
拷贝了一份给她男朋友
was copy it and give it to her boyfriend.
我太兴奋了
I'm so excited.
Max 这就是我高兴时候的样子
Max, this is what I look like when I'm happy.
你从来没看到过
You've never seen it.
请叫我的新名字 克拉米迪娅 卡戴珊
Please call me by my new name, Khlamydia Kardashian.
千万别说这样的傻话
Don't say anything stupid like that.
我什么都不会说的
I won't have to say anything.
克丽斯看到我的嘴唇和大胸
Kris will see me and recognize me
以及我想住富人区的念想
as one of her own with my lips, my boobs,
就会觉得我是她亲生的
and my willingness to live in some place called Calabasas.
他们来了 我的人生要改变了!
They're here. My life changes now!
这就是我高兴时候的样子
This is what I look like happy.
你从来没看到过
You've never seen it.
嗨 我们真的是非常兴奋
Hi, we are so, so excited about this.
情况有变
There has been a change.
她们不来了
They're not coming.
穿高跟鞋走过来太远了
It's too far to walk in heels.
看看 她也许真的是我亲妈
See? She might as well have been my real mom
因为她选了高跟鞋而不要我
'cause she just chose a heel over me.
嗨 我是来见我的闺蜜金金的
Hi, here I am to meet Kiki, my bff.
看看我的新裙子! 和她同款的!
And look at my new dress! Twinsies!
肯定是同款
They certainly are.
抱歉 她不来了
Sorry, she's not coming.
我们在姜巴果汁店取景了
We had to film them in Jamba Juice instead.
噢
Oh.
这真是超级尴尬的
Well, this is super awkward.
愚蠢的卡戴珊姐妹!
Stupid Kardashians!
金 大脚踝 臭脾气
Kim, Kankels, Krank,
小的那俩叫"性爱运动"和"儿童足球"
and the little ones, Kegel and Kickball,
才不屑你们拍马屁呢
You can kiss my keister.
Max 停下! 我想睡觉
Max, stop it! I'm trying to sleep.
抱歉 但我很生气 反正也11点半了
Well, sorry, but I'm pissed and it's 11:30 anyway.
你怎么了?
What's going on?
金哪怕发一条状态 她那两千两百万的
Even one tweet from Kim would have exposed us
粉丝就会知道我们了
to 22 million followers.
基督教科学派都没那么多教众
Scientology doesn't even have those numbers.
我们被耍了 我就知道
They screwed us. I know.
所以我在为卡戴珊姐妹
That is why I'm making hate cupcakes
做恶意满满纸杯蛋糕 瞧
for the Kardashians, see?
"吃屎" "去死"
"Eat it," "Bite me,"
还有这三个... "找" "攻" "做"
and these three... "Get" "A" "Job."
还有一个以防万一 是给她妈妈做的
Oh, and one for the mom that says, "I still love you,"
"我还爱你"
just in case.
快点起床
Now come on, get up.
你儿子要出去散步拉屎了
Your son needs to go out and take an 8-foot crap.
不 我罢工了
No, I'm done.
如果大家都不要纸杯蛋糕了 我也不要了
If everyone's done with cupcakes, so am I.
我不想再假装一切都会顺利了
I'm done pretending that everything's gonna work out.
在我们的真人秀里 一切都糟透了
In our reality show, it's not.
听好了 现在起床 不然我就把你连床一起合起来
Look, get up, or I will close this bed with you in it,
你的新真人秀就是"真人真事: 我住在墙里"
and your new reality show will be True Life: I live in a wall.
我绝对不会起床的
I'm not getting up. Ever.
啊! Max 住手! 住手!
Aah! Max, stop, stop it! Stop it!
放我下来! 放我下来!
Put me down! Put me down!
怎么了?
What's happening?
我抬不起头了
I can't lift my head.
是不是中风了?
Did I have a stroke?
冷静点 没人在你床上中风过
Calm down. No one has stroked in your bed
除非... 做上一年?
Since... What is it, going on a year?
Max 我的头发被夹住了
Max. My hair is caught.
我的头发被夹住了! 我的头发被夹住了!
My hair is caught! My hair is caught!
你在对谁吼呢?
Who are you yelling at?
这该死的状况! 想想办法!
The whole situation! Do something!
我来看看
Let me look.
没错 都卷进床的齿轮里了
Oh yeah, it's all caught up in the bed gears here.
天啊 我的床竟然有齿轮
Oh my god, I have a bed with gears
我的头发还被夹住了!
and my hair is caught in it!
不行
Ooh, nope.
真的完全卷进去了
It's really all stuck up in there.
太奇怪了
It's so odd.
真不知道怎么会发生这种事
I don't know how a thing like this could happen.
是你要把我翻到墙上的
Uh, you put me up into the wall.
现在我被卡在折叠床上
And now I'm trapped in a murphy bed
就像个倒霉版的长发公主
like some welfare rapunzel.
别惊慌 我有剪刀
Stop panicking, I'll get a scissors.
对 没错! 快去拿剪刀
Oh, yeah, yeah! Get the scissors.
然后一下扎进我胸口 因为要剪头发
Then plunge 'em into my heart 'cause I'd rather die
我宁愿死
than cut my hair.
好吧 Max 我想到办法了
Okay, Max, I think I have something that might work,
但你得保证
but you have to promise me
不会再提起这件事
that you will never bring this up again.
什么事? 你的头卡在
What? The fact that your head
床上这件事?
is stuck to your bed?
抱歉 我肯定会再提的
Sorry, that's coming up again.
去翻我的床头柜
Go into my nightstand
然后把我那瓶肉桂味的卸妆油拿出来
and get my cinnamon-flavored make-up remover.
你是说润滑油吧?
You mean the lube?
我们能不能就叫它卸妆油?
Can we please call it make-up remover?
求你了! 就这样叫吧
Please! I need us to do that.
快用完了
It's almost empty.
天啊 你还真是卸了很多妆
Man, you've removed a lot of make-up.
别说了! 挤点出来
Stop it! Just squeeze some out
涂到我们想要润滑的部位
and put it on the parts that we need to move.
这个我在行
Yeah, I'm familiar.
呃!
Ew!
拜托告诉我这方法有用
Please tell me it's working.
我在试 但我觉得没法把你的头发救出来
I'm trying, but I don't think I can get your hair out.
好消息是 我觉得可以轻松插入了
Good news is, I think we can fit a penis in there.
会是谁?
Who could that be?
我们经常为之卖命的强奸犯
A rapist we've done most of the work for.
我们正好说到你
Oh, we were just talking about you.
Max 你得帮我做Han要的土司面包
Max, you gotta help me with the bread for Han's toast.
我已经烤焦十条了
I've already burned ten of these.
事实证明我能成功烤出来的只有兴奋剂
Turns out the only thing I can successfully bake is meth.
Oleg 快到床上来 我需要你!
Oleg, come to the bed. I need you!
好啊!
All right!
尽管等了四年时间 但我就在这里 宝贝
Only took you four years, but I'm here, baby.
不 不是你想的那样 Oleg
No, it's not like that, Oleg.
快点过来!
Just get over here!
好的
Okay.
拿好
Hold this.
Earl 你在这里干什么?
Earl, what are you doing here?
Oleg打电话给我 说他没法让Caroline
Oleg called me when he couldn't get Caroline
停止尖叫
to stop the screaming.
Max 嗨 Earl分了我一块布朗宁
Hi, Max. Earl gave me part of a brownie.
事实证明 青光眼和头发被夹住
Turns out, glaucoma and having hair stuck
治疗的方子完全一样
take the exact same prescription.
快看!
Look!
这就对了 伙计们!
That's right, you mothers!
我做到了!
I did it!
我烤出了完美的面包!
I made the perfect bread!
你是个厨师 却花了19个小时才做出一条面包
You're a chef who took 19 hours to make one loaf of bread.
史蒂芬·霍金百米跑的成绩都比你好
Stephen Hawking was more successful at the 100-yard dash.
还有你... 你知不知道
And you... You are aware
我跑去曼哈顿 给金·卡戴珊
that I went all the way into Manhattan,
住的酒店送了一堆恶意纸杯蛋糕
cupcake-bombed Kim Kardashian's hotel,
结果回来你竟然还躺着
and you're still just laying here, right?
你不用嘘嘘吗?
Didn't you have to pee?
大部分尿我都憋住了
I held most of it in.
真是疯了 你都这样一整天了
This is crazy. You've been here all day.
我们还是把你的头发剪掉吧
Let's just cut your damn hair already.
没了头发 我就不是我了
I wouldn't be me without my hair.
我活不下去的
I can't live without it.
你能活下去
Yes, you can.
没有钱 没有电
You have lived without money,
没人陪你做活塞运动
you've lived without electricity,
你不都活下来了
you've lived without plumbing.
你觉得我是靠什么撑过来的?
What do you think got me through it?
我的头发
My hair.
我就想 "钱都没了 马桶堵了
I'd be like, "Lost all my money, the toilet's clogged,
幸好我的头发还在"
still got my hair."
亲爱的 我想那些布朗宁可能不够劲
Darling, I don't think those brownies are kicking in.
我还有棒棒糖哦
I also have some lollipops.
我希望你满意了
I hope you're happy.
猫眼里什么都没看到
I didn't see anything through the peep-hole,
所以我猜是Han来了
so I'm guessing it's Han.
你们好!
Ah, hello!
餐厅开门了 员工却没影了!
I have an open diner and no diner staff!
Han 看呀 我做出了完美的面包
Han, look, I made perfect bread.
哇 这比我习惯的尺寸要大得多
Oh, wow. It's bigger than I'm used to.
让我冷静一下 深呼吸
Let me just take a minute and breathe.
我确信自己可以完全吞进去
And I'm sure I can take it all in.
如果你需要帮助
Well, if you need any help,
Caroline有卸妆油的
Caroline's got some make-up remover.
金金发了 金金发了 金金发了!
Kiki tweet, Kiki tweet, Kiki tweet!
她是在说"金金发了"!
She's saying "Kiki tweet"!
他怎么听懂呢? 难道他是海豚人?
How did he understand that? Is he part dolphin?
金·卡戴珊发了我那些恶意蛋糕的照片
Kim Kardashian tweeted a pic of my mean cupcakes
然后写着 "Max的手工纸杯蛋糕 #不厚道"
and said, "Max's homemade cupcakes #notcool."
天啊 金·卡戴珊竟然讨厌我认识的人了!
Oh, my God, Kim Kardashian hates someone I know!
两千两百万的粉丝都看到了!
That went out to 22 million people!
- 我很抱歉  - 干嘛道歉?
- I'm so sorry.  - Why?
你知道有多少人受不了卡戴珊姐妹吗?
Do you know how many people can't stand the Kardashians?
我们的蛋糕店窗口会被挤爆的!
Our cupcake window will be packed!
快来剪掉
Cut me loose.
嘿 Caroline 我们终于要动剪刀了
Hey, Caroline, we're finally about to scissor.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
我们有生意要做
We got a business to run.
快剪 我不会有事的
Cut it, I'll be fine.
啊!
Aah!
好吧 你还是吃根棒棒糖吧
Yeah, you're gonna need that lollipop.
我明白 卡戴珊姐妹最讨厌了
Yeah, I know, those Kardashians are the worst.
所以我再也不跟她们同行了
That's why I don't keep up with them anymore.
好了 Max 挺不错的
All right, Max. Okay, that's it.
只剩一个了 是不错
Just one left. Not bad.
你的发型也不错
And your hair's not bad either.
现在是不错
Yeah, now,
幸好我及时赶到发廊
after the emergency trip to that salon.
在你刚剪完的时候
When you got done with me,
我看上去就像只做过化疗的小鸟
I looked like a baby bird on chemo.
抱歉我花光了最后的积蓄去剪了这个头发
I'm sorry I had to use the last of our savings for my hair cut.
- 你才不抱歉  - 没错 我爱这个发型
- No, you're not.  - No, I am not, I love this.
嗨 我是金
Hi, I'm Kim.
我只是想来道歉
I just wanted to say sorry
我们那天没有过来拍摄
that we didn't film here the other day.
光看着她 我就快被亮瞎了
It almost hurts to look at her.
我知道你们两个为了生意
I know how hard us girls really work
有多努力工作
to keep our businesses going,
所以我会买个小蛋糕
so I'll take a cupcake
然后认认真真发一条微博
and I'll totally tweet about it for real.
太谢谢你了
Thank you so much.
这个蛋糕 拿着 拿着
Here, here, here, here, here.
100块的我们找不开 无所谓了
We can't break a $100, and anyway,
这个就当我们请的
this is so on the house.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
发型很不错
Cute hair.
等等 就一个问题...
Wait. Real quick...
你觉得你妈妈会收养我吗?
Do you think your mother would adopt me?
这真是超级尴尬的
This is super awkward.